Hear me, humans!
I shall leave Ente Isla in your hands today!
But know this: I shall return
to subjugate you and all of Ente Isla!
So, they've fled through the Gate.
What shall we do?
Follow them, obviously.
You do realize we have no
idea what's on the other side?
I don't care what world he
runs to... it won't do any good.
I will find him.
I'll find him, and I'll defeat
him with my own hands.
Right here, this moment,
this is our starting point
Let's picture what we might be able to do
Unbelievable things can happen sometimes
More... we can push past this
---------------------------------------------------------------------
樱律联萌站 http://bbs.ylbud.com/
Everything is born from zero;
I want to shine, flap my wings hard
樱律联萌站为您带来高质量中日双语字幕
中日双语字幕由 樱律字幕组 制作
感谢以下成员倾情制作
听译：五月、吉禾　校对：jez　时间轴：咲夜　后期：OMG
And fly to that sky
Come on, let's go, with
brilliant smiles on our faces!
Let's fly off to an unknown world right now
I decide, I'm the one who chooses my future
Let's follow our dreams
Sure, some days we'll cry
It's a precious wish, don't disappear
I'm going after the future you,
because I know I'll find you
"The Devil is a Part-Timer!"
The Hero Stays at the Devil's
Castle for Work Reasons
勇者、仕事優先で魔王城に泊まる
Why are you working part-time at
the Hatagaya MgRonald's, Satan?
魔王サタン
なざ貴方が幡ヶ谷のマクドナルドでアルバイトをしてるの
Emilia the hero? Forget me,
what are you doing here?!
勇者エミリヤ
お前こそ、何でここにいる
I leapt through the Gate after you,
in order to take you down.
貴方達をゲートに飛び込んだ
貴方を倒すために
Emilia, wait, I can explain!
待ってエミリヤ
話せば分ける
I don't want to hear it. Prepare to die, Satan!
問答無用
覚悟、魔王
Hey, Emilia.
おい、エミリヤ
Shut up. I'm not going to chat with you!
黙れ、貴様と話をするつもりはない
It's just, that knife...
いや、そのナイフ
Isn't that from the 100-yen shop in Sasazuka?
笹塚の百金で売ってるヤツじゃないか
S-So what?!
それが何を
What happened to your sacred sword?
お前、聖剣はどうした
Th-That's none of your business!
そ、そんなこと貴方には関係ないわ
Have you lost your celestial force, by any chance?
もしかして聖法気失ったんじゃないのか
Or maybe you just can't afford to waste it?
もしくは無駄使いできないとか
Well, you're in the same boat, aren't you?!
それは貴方も同じでしょう
The magic I sense from you now is nothing
compared to what it was in Ente Isla!
エンテイスラの時と比べものにならないほど
脆弱な魔力しか感じられないわ
Well, yeah...
まぁ、そりゃそうだけど
Sword or no sword, a Devil with no magic
聖剣などなくても
魔力失いアルバイトで生活する魔王なんて恐れるに足らず
who's working fast-food jobs is
hardly a formidable adversary!
Prepare yourself!
覚悟っ！
Oh dear. Those are precious ingredients...
貴重な食材が
His Majesty sure is late.
魔王様、遅いな
Metropolitan Police Department East Yoyogi Police Station
West Sasazuka Outpost
Well? Why were you fighting
in the middle of the street?
何であんなところで喧嘩してたの
To take him down.
この人を倒すためです
"Take him down"?
倒す？
Look, I don't know what your boyfriend did,
あのね、彼氏が何したかはしらないけどね
but whatever it was, no knife fights!
刃物はダメだよ、刃物は
B-Boyfriend?
か、彼氏
He probably thinks that was
a lovers' quarrel or something.
痴話喧嘩かなんかと思われてんだろう
I am not in a romantic
relationship with this man!
私とコイツとはそういう関係じゃ
Fine, but if you're breaking up,
とにかく、別れ話とかちゃんとお互い話し合って
you need to just talk it over
like reasonable adults, okay?
もっと穏やか　ね
I'll let you slide for today.
今日はこのくらいにしといてあげるは
Huh?
あ？
But just this once. I've memorized your address.
でも次はないわよ
貴方の住所暗記したから
Tonight will be the last good
night's sleep you'll ever have.
明日から枕高くして眠れる日はないと思いなさい
Hey, that doesn't sound like
the kind of thing a hero should say.
お前、とても勇者の言う台詞とは思えないぞ
I don't want to hear that from a part-timer Devil!
バイト暮らしの魔王に言われたくないわよ
Whatever, give me back my
umbrella, you 100-yen hero!
百金勇者、それより貸して傘、かえってよ
You said I could toss it when I was done.
用は済んだら捨ててよかったでしょう
I took it neatly apart and
put it in the trash for you.
綺麗に分解してやったわ
How could you?!
ヒッデ
I'm a hero; I wouldn't leave an
umbrella from the Devil just lying around.
勇者たる私は魔王に借りたなんて傘おいてわけないでしょう
Wh-What a pain...
面倒くせい
Anyway, starting tomorrow you'd
better watch your back at night!
とにかく、明日から夜道気をつけることね
She sure doesn't seem heroic to me...
まったく勇者らしくねいな
Yes, Sir, in that case...
はい、そうしたまずは
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
申し訳ございません
Please select "Call Rate" from the menu...
メニュからの通話料金の
Again, my name is Yusa, and I thank
you for allowing me to assist you today.
はい、ありがとうございました
本日は遊佐が承りました
Aw, man, there are way
too many complaints today!
もう今日くれも多すぎ
Try cracking open the manual
for a change, why don't you!
ちっと自分で目にわる読めずな
Hey, wanna grab lunch at that new
curry place that opened last week?
お昼そう、先週オープンしたカレー屋に見てみない
Hmm, it might be crowded this time of day...
この時間込んでるじゃないかな
Okay then, should we give up
and do MgR's for today?
じゃ、今回は諦めてマクドにしますか
Anything but that. Sorry.
それだけはいや、ごめん
"Answer"
Ugh, another one.
あぁ、来た
Oh, well. Back to work!
しかたない、仕事、仕事
Thank you for calling the Docodemo Customer
Service Center. How may I help you?
おとい合わせ、ありがとうございます
どこでも、たいやぱセンターでございます
"Bargain Price - Tissues"
"Bargain Price - Toilet Paper"
"Main Dishes and Sides - Shimashima Deli"
It's time for "Crash That Dinner!"
爆撃！隣の夕ご飯
Crash
That Dinner!
All right, let's visit this house here!
じゃ、早速、こちらお宅お邪魔しましょう
Wow, suddenly I'm smelling something lovely!
何かいきなり素敵なにおい来ましたよ
Why, this is just sumptuous!
Is that steak I see?! Lovely!
あぁ、御精です
奥さん、ステーキじゃないですか
ステーキ、今日何かお祝いですか
Are you celebrating something today?
Now I see why it smells so good!
Look here, cameraman!
いい匂いがそるわけですよ
カメラさん、ほら
You're using high-quality
meat, aren't you, Ma'am?
いいお肉作った、奥さん
Could this be a cut that
costs 20,000 yen a gram?
もしかしてこのお肉二万円ぐらいするお肉なんか
No? It's not?!
- Argh, at this rate I'm doing the same thing he is!
- Ninety-eight yen?! You're kidding!
って、これじゃアイツとやってること何も変わりないじゃない
Wish we had a little more protein.
もう少し蛋白素ほしいな
You eat hamburgers on almost a daily basis, Sire.
ほぼ毎日ハンバーガー食べてるじゃありませんか
The MHK guy?
ＮＨＫか
He came yesterday.
昨日来ました
Newspaper salesman?
新聞か
I would think they're fully aware
that we can't afford a subscription...
家に新聞購読余裕はないことは
Hello, to whom do we owe the pleasure?
はい、どちら様ですか
Well, I thank you for that most
courteous greeting, Demon General Alciel.
どちら様ではご丁寧挨拶いってみはね
悪魔大元帥アルシエル
You do remember Emilia the hero, I assume?
まさか忘れたわけじゃないでしょうね
勇者エミリヤの名を
E-Emilia the hero?!
勇者エミリヤだと
Now open this door right now!
Accept your punishment with good grace!
さぁ、早くこの門はあけなさい
大人しく成敗される
Hey!
ほら
- Sire! It's the hero! The hero is here!
- How dare you lock me out!
魔王様、勇者です
勇者が現れました
- Y-Yeah, I know.
- Come on, open up!
あ、分かってる
- Did you know about this, Sire?
- You're in there too, aren't you, Satan?!
Give up and open this door!
ひょっとして、ご存知だったんです
- Yeah. Sorry I didn't tell you.
- Hey! Hurry up!
ちょっと、ほら、早く
いや、黙って悪かったんけど
- I ran into her yesterday
on my way home from work.
- I'll kick this thing open! You okay with that?
昨日あったんバイトの帰道
蹴るわよ、いいよ
I'll kick it!
蹴るよ
- The police mistook it for a lovers' quarrel.
- You want that?!
警察に痴話喧嘩と間違われた
I've never been so mortified in my life!
Me, dating the ruler of demons?!
私の人生最大の恥辱よ
魔王とカンプルと思われる何て
- Open up! Let me in right now!
あけなさいよ
- And might I ask why you didn't tell me, Sire?
- Open up! Let me in right now!
そのようなことどうしてお知らせくださらなかったですか
- And might I ask why you didn't tell me, Sire?
- I'm getting it out!
- Well, I figured she didn't do any real damage, so...
- I'm getting it out, you hear me?!
いや、別に実害ないかなと思って
- And it looked like she couldn't
use her powers, just like we can't.
- Open up! Hey! Hurry up...
それにアイツと私達同じで聖法気使えねいみたいだったし
- The hero has no way to replenish her
heavenly power in this world, either...
- Open the door!
勇者もまだこの世界ではてんの力補充する術持たないということ
- The hero has no way to replenish her
heavenly power in this world, either...
- Hey! Come on...
- In other words, she has no
power to control the gate?
- Hey!
つまり、ゲートを正用する力がないと
Aw, let her in.
おい、入れてやれ
I swear I'll kick it in...
あけろうよ
This room is awful...
ひどい部屋
It's shabby, it's tiny,
and it's got paper-thin walls.
ぼろし、狭いし、音悪い声だし
Wow, that's just mean.
ヒッデ言われよう
The Devil's Castle prioritizes
functionality over comfort.
魔王城は居住性より機能性を重視する
"Functionality"? That's a laugh.
And what's with the pathetic dinner?
機能は聞いて呆れるはよ
それにそれ寂しい夕食
Hey, Ashiya is amazing! He whips up
meals out of nothing, almost like magic!
あしやはすごいんだぞ
何もないところから魔法のように飯を作る
I am honored by your kind praise, Sire.
お褒めに扱り光栄でございます、魔王様
No prob.
Are you stupid?
馬鹿じゃないわ
I can't believe the ruler of demons
is dining on konjac and cucumbers!
魔王は蒟蒻とキュウリだけの夕飯何て
Got a problem with that? We're poor.
悪いかよ、貧乏なんだよ
Yes, I do!
悪いじゃないよ、何よ
Did I seriously travel to another world
to kill a broken-down guy like this?!
こんな草臥れたヤツを殺すために世界を渡ったの
It's pathetic! Even I live better
than this, and I live alone!
最低よ
一人暮らしの私だってもうちょっと益しな生活しているわよ
Your comrades aren't here?
お前仲間いないのか
Shut up!
煩い
One of the high priests was
supposed to come with me.
本当は大神官が一緒に来るはずだったのよ
We were going to come home
as soon as we defeated you!
貴方を倒すたら、さっさと帰ることになってたのに
But then... But then!
それなのに
得快点 奥鲁巴
Olba, hurry! The gate's about to close!
门就要关上了
I can see that!
我知道了
Make it in time...
赶上了
We made it, Olba!
奥鲁巴
Olba?
那个 奥鲁巴？
No way!
骗人的吧？
Olba!
奥鲁巴
I ended up coming here alone.
私一人こっちに来ちゃだもん
That's rough.
そりゃ気の毒に
I don't want your pity.
貴方に同情なんかされたくないのよ
You're like a search party that
needs its own search party.
我々追うって迷子では、ただの二重遭難ではないか
Well, I guess you'd better find a way home fast.
まぁ、さっさと帰る方法を見つけることだな
You may have found us, but we don't
have the money to move anywhere else.
俺達はお前に見つかったらって
引越す金もない
That's why we're living here.
だからここに住んでる
I'm beginning my new attempt at
world conquest from this Devil's Castle!
この魔王城から俺の新たな世界征服事業は始める
Can you? You don't even have a full-time job.
フリーな貴方はそんなことできるの
If you think I'm just living a peaceful
part-timer's life, you're dead wrong.
俺はただ安穏アルバイト生活を送ってると思ったら
大間違いた
I intend to conquer Japan!
俺は日本を征服するつもりている
For your information,
マクドナルドにはな
MgRonald's has a system where part-timers
can become regular employees!
アルバイトは正社員になれるシステムがあるんだ
Hear me, Emilia: I shall become
a regular employee in this world!
いいか、エミリヤ
俺はこの世界で正社員になってみせる
And thus I shall accumulate
wealth and social status,
そして金と社会地位を積み重ね
become a powerful figure who makes
all manner of humans kneel before me,
多くの人間の跪いた実力者になり
and then invade Ente Isla once more!
再びエンテイスラ攻め込んだ
That's ludicrous.
馬鹿馬鹿しい
I'm sure a mere human like you
can't understand my lofty aims.
俺の崇高な志を人間如き理解できるとは思っていない
I suspect she understands all too well, Sire.
多分、十二分に理解していると思います
Somehow I just don't care anymore.
何かどうでもよくちゃった
I'm going home. I have work tomorrow.
帰る
明日も仕事だし
Don't go getting the wrong idea, though.
でも勘違いしないてよね
If I used my remaining power,
I could kill you any time I wanted.
残った力を使えば貴方を殺すなんていつでもできるんだから
So why don't you?
じゃ、何でやらねんだよう
Because if I use it all up, I won't
be able to get home to Ente Isla.
力を使え切るとはエンテイスラに帰れなくなるからわよ
So I'll let you live until
I figure out my way home.
だから期間の目処はつくまでは命を取らないておいてあげる
Oh, and in Japan my name
is Emi Yusa. Don't slip up.
それと、日本での私の名前は遊佐恵美よ、間違えないて
Sadao
Maou
Shiro
Ashiya
Sadao
Maou
What's with the name "Sadao," anyway?
それにしても、さだおって何を
Nobody in this generation is named that!
今も時の若者の名前じゃないわね
Apologize to all the Sadaos in Japan for that!
日本全国のさだおに謝れ
Emi, you've been really
stressed lately, haven't you?
恵美、何か最近ストレス貯まってでしょう
Wanna go get a bite to eat after work?
この後、ご飯一緒にいかない
Hmmm... Well, I have
something to do this evening...
そうね、今夜はちょっと用があるから
So, did you finally get a boyfriend?
ひょっとして、男でもできた
"Yusa"
It's not like that!
そういうんじゃないから
There's no way the Devil is just
innocently living the poor life.
魔王はただ大人しく
貧乏生活を送ってるわけないわ
I can't let him out of my sight.
目を離すわけには
Aw, come on, you can just go by yourself!
何だよ、お前一人できればいいじゃねいか
I cannot do this alone!
The task requires your powers, Sire.
私一人ではダメなのです
ここは魔王様の力必要なのです
Come, let us hurry!
さぁ、急ぎますよ
Jeez, it's fine, they're not gonna run out!
大丈夫だって、なくなってしないよ
You don't take this battle seriously enough!
魔王様は甘く見すぎです
Where are they going at this time of day?
二人って、こんな時間にどこへ
"Flash Sale"
"Today Only: Medium Eggs ¥98"
Let's get back in line later
and buy one more carton each.
後、もう一回並んでで
もう碗バクつづ買いましょう
No, that's against the rules.
いや、それはルール違反だ
Emi, want to go out to dinner tonight?
恵美、夜何か食べにいかない
Sorry, I have to run some errands.
ごめん、今日これから用事があるのよ
Ashiya, I'm leaving you behind!
あしや、先に行くぞ
There's no time to waste!
We're going to the bath!
もはや、一刻のゆうゆうおれ
銭湯（戦闘）に向かうぞ
- Please, Sire, wait! I just need to lock the door!
- As in bloodbath? Who are they fighting?!
魔王様、お待ちください
戦闘、一体何と戦うってのよ
Phew, we made it in time.
間に合いましたね
Man, I wish they'd keep
bathhouses open 24 hours!
銭湯も二十四時間にしてほしいなぁ
Maybe when I conquer Japan, my first
act will be to make a 24-hour one!
まず日本を征服したら
二十四時間営業の風呂屋をつくるか
Come on, you'll come out
with me tonight, right?
ね、今夜は付き合ってくれるんでしょう
Hmm? U-Umm...
You're busy again?!
また用事？
I-I'm sorry.
ご、ごめんね
So, you put men before friendship.
友情より男ですか
I told you, it's not like that!
だから違うってば
Sire, please don't!
おいやめてください　魔王様
Sadao
Maou
But anyone would be curious
about this demonic experiment!
いやだって気になるだろう
この悪魔の実験を
"Demonic," my foot! Quit being ridicu...
何が悪魔ですか
怠けたこと
あ　あ
Whoa, it's just like Chi said!
わっほんとだ
千ちゃんといってたどおりだ
You try some, too! It does
taste like melon! Just a little!
お前も食ってみろよ
メロンっぽい味がする
少しだけ
"Melon," my foot!
何がメロンですが
- A cucumber is a cucumber,
whether you put honey on it or not!
- Maybe I'll go home...
帰ろうかな
きゅうりは蜂蜜付けなんてきゅうりはきゅうりです
Now you listen to me, Sire!
いいですか魔王様
Only people with leeway in
their budgets can eat like this!
このような食べ方は
生活に余裕のある人間のすること
Don't you have any leeway in your heart?
お前にはここの余裕がないのか
I don't appreciate the snarky comeback!
何ですかその嫌な切り返しは？！
In any case, if you crave melon
enough to mix cucumbers and honey,
第一きゅうりと蜂蜜でメロンを味わいたいなら
you're better off just buying a melon!
メロンを買ったほうがいいでしょう
What is it?
何ですか？
An earthquake.
地震。。。。
Don't try to distract me!
ごまかさないでください！
Sheesh, what's your problem?
なんだよもう
Don't you "sheesh" me! Sheesh!
もうではありませんよもう！！
- Teehee!
- King Satan!
ぷぷ～
魔王様！
Welcome.
いらっしゃい
May I have a moment?
ちょっといいかしら
Are you ready to order, Miss?
ご注文はおきまりでしょうか
I need to speak with you outside.
外で話があるんだけど
Takeout, got it.
出かどですね
When you get off work, meet me
at the intersection where we met.
バイトが終わったらこの前の交差点でまってるから
I won't take no for an answer.
きょひけんは認めないわよ
Would you like to make that a meal?
セットでよろしすか
Come alone.
一人できなさい
Okay, just the sandwich, then.
単品ですね
かしこまりました
One Big Mag burger, please!
ビッグマグロバーガー　one please～
I don't plan to fight you. Make sure you show up.
戦うつもりはないわ
必ず来なさい
Thanks a bunch! Step over to
the side, please, it'll be right out!
あぞ～す　わきへずれて少々お待ちくださやせ～
What a pain.
めんどくせい
That customer was kind of weird, huh?
なんか変わったお客さんでしたね
Yep. It takes all kinds, as they say.
そうな
いろいろな人がいるからね
It looked like you two were talking
about something. Do you know her?
何かお話してたみたいですけど
お知り合いですか
We have a bit of a history.
まあ　ちょっとご縁が合ってね
は？なんか怪しい
I'm suspicious!
Why?
何が？
She was sort of pretty, wasn't she?
Wasn't she?! Wasn't she, Mr. Maou?!
確かにちょっと美人さんでしたもんね！
ね!真奥さん！ね！
Don't say "wasn't she" three times!
ねって三回も言わないで
What's with you, Chi? She and I aren't...
千ちゃん何よ
俺があの女と　あっ
Welcome to MgRonald's! I can take
your order whenever you're ready.
いらっしゃいませ
ご注文決まりましたどうぞ
Women's
Changing Room
できた～
I'm heading out, Mr. Maou!
お先に失礼します真奥さん～
Mmm! Night, Chi!
お疲れ　千ちゃん
Good niiiight!
お疲れ様で～す
Mr. Maou!
真奥さん！
Yeah?
え？
Were you okay in yesterday's earthquake?
昨日の地震　大丈夫でした？
Earthquake?
地震？
Oh, yeah, there was one.
My roommate didn't feel it, though.
そう言えばあったな
同居人は気づかなかったみたいけど
Roommate?!
同居人？！
- What do you mean, "okay"?
- What? Are we talking about the roommate?
平気でどういう意味？
へっ同居人ですか？
No, the earthquake.
じゃなくて　地震
What? Oh! It hit my place really hard.
うん？あ。。。
あっち　広がったんですよ
When I got home from school, all my
books and CDs had fallen off the shelves.
学校から帰ってきたら
本とかCDとか全部起こっちゃってた
Huh?! The earthquake wasn't that big!
へえ？！そんなに地震大きくなかったけど
Yes, I asked my friends at school, too,
はい
学校の友達にも聞いていましたが
but for some reason it was
only my place that got hit hard.
なぜか内だけでした　広がったの
By the way, Mr. Maou!
ところで真奥さん！！
Wha... Yes?!
へ？！はい！
A minute ago... you said
something about a roommate...!
先ほど　その
同居人がどうだか
Y-Yeah...
Might that roommate be of
a g-g-g-girlfriendly sort?!
それで　ああのう。。かかか彼女
その　　何かだったりですかね
Nah, a guy. I'm living the poor life with
an old servant... I mean, friend of mine.
ああ　昔からの部下
じゃなくて
男友達と貧乏生活をしてるのは
Oh, I see! Thank goodness!
へ～そうなんですか
は～よかった～
For what?!
なにが？
Well? What do you want to talk about?
で　話って何だよ
I want you to tell me something:
ひとつ聞かせてもらおうと思って
Would you like to live in this world forever?
あなた　この世界でずっと暮らそうとは思わない
Excuse me?!
は？
Of course not! Where did that come from?
思うわけないだろう
いきなりなに言い出すんだ
I've seen your attitude at work and
at home over the past several days.
この数日間
あなたの勤務態度は
生活態度　見せてもらったわ
Are you a stalker now?
ストーカーかよ
You haven't done anything evil,
and you're living a simple, serious life.
悪事を働くこともなく
疾走でまじめな暮らし
You're trusted by your manager
and younger coworkers alike,
店長からも後輩からも信頼され
and you deal with customers with
an ease supported by confidence.
地震に裏打ちされた柔軟な対応力
You're the ideal MgR's worker.
まさに理想なマグドのクルーね
Am I from Kansai now?
関西心かよ
I was ready to write off what
you said the other day as a joke,
この前のあなたの話
戯言と聞き流しそうになったけど
but now I'm starting to think
there was some truth to it.
あながちうそでもないじゃないかと思えてきたの
If you're willing to spend the
rest of your life in this world,
このままあなたが
この世界で人生を過ごしてくれるなら
I don't feel a need to defeat
you just for the sake of it.
私は無理にあなたを倒そうとは思わないわ
Why don't you stay in Sasazuka for good?
このまま笹塚に骨をうずめたら
Is telling men to live with other men
forever a thing for you or something?
お前は男と二人で終生共に暮らすような生活を
人に勧める趣味でもあんのか
Give up on Ente Isla and find a new life here.
エンテーイスラはあきらめて
ここで新しい生活を見つけなさい
ふん！ありえない
Not a chance.
I swear I'll return to conquer Ente Isla.
俺は必ずエンテーイスラを征服しに戻る
- Wh-What?
- Pathetic... Is he really the Devil?
情けない
- Gah, a flat tire?! Get it together, Dullahan!
- Pathetic... Is he really the Devil?
あいつ本当に魔王なの
あ!!バイク　しっかりしろあんこ
You died right after I bought you!
買ったばかりで言ってしまって
もう何を　大げさな
What's with the melodrama?
You can get a flat fixed for 1,000 yen!
パンクぐらい千円で直してくれるわよ
Really?! Then I'll go first
thing in the morning and...
ほんとか？！
じゃあ明日　朝市で
Hey, are we...
俺たち　ひょっとして
...being shot at?!
打たれてる？
There are holes in the sign!
看板に穴が
Hey, don't touch me!
ちょっと触らないでよ
Is this really the time to argue?!
けんかしてる場合じゃネイだろう
Heh, you're pretty good.
やるじゃないか
I am a hero, you know. Don't underestimate me.
これでも勇者よ
馬鹿にしないで
So, would you mind getting off of me?
それじゃ俺の上からどいてくれ
You're the one who let me land on you!
あなたが勝手に私の下地来になったんじゃない
There should still be plenty of people
at Sasazuka Station. Can you run?
笹塚の駅なら
まだ人が大勢いるはずだ
走れるか
I'm faster than you are,
guy who takes it easy riding a bike.
自転車なんか乗って楽してるあなたより速いわよ
You're on. Let's go!
ちょうど　いくぞ
Guess they're... not following us this far, huh?
どうやら　ここまで追ってこない
みたいだな
What was that about?
何だったの今の
Dunno, but... that was no ordinary sniper...
わかんないけど
ただの狙撃者ね
Those bullets were made of magic energy.
魔力エネルギーいたんだ
Magic?! Which means...
魔力？
ということは
We're dealing with someone pretty powerful.
相当の力の持ち主
And someone who knows who we are.
しかも俺とお前の正体を知っている
Is there such a person?
そんなやついるの
A mystery sniper just showed up when
a demon king and a hero were in one place.
魔王と勇者が揃った場所に
なぞの狙撃だ
The natural assumption is that
this has to do with Ente Isla.
エンテーイスラ絡みだと考えのが普通だろう
Look at the trouble you got me into!
お前のせいでとんでも目にあった
Y-You think it's my fault?!
私のせい？！
If you'd picked a safer place and time,
this wouldn't have happened.
お前はもっと穏やかな時間と場所を設定してれば
こんな騒ぎは起きなかったろう
That's yourfault for working so late!
あんたがこんな時間までバイトしてるからでしょう
Why not meet in the afternoon?
別に昼だっていいじゃん
I work in the afternoon!
昼は私がバイトしてるのよ
Well don't blame me for that!
しらネイよそんなこと
Hey! Where are you going?!
ちょっと　どこ行くのよ
Home. Gotta be at work early tomorrow.
帰るんだよ
明日もバイトが早い
You're just going to run off by yourself?!
一人で逃げる気？
Of course!
当たり前だ
You be careful getting home, too. See you!
お前も気をつけて帰るよ　じゃなあ
Look, do you intend to launch
a night raid or something?
お前は　これから要地でもかける気なのかな
N-No.
そ、そんなんじゃないわよ
Then what's the big idea?
Our landlady lives right next door!
だったらなんだよ
大家さんだってすぐ近くに住んでんだ
I'd rather avoid her, so no making a scene, okay?
できれば会いたくネイから
騒ぎは起こさないでくれよ
Wh-What is it?
ど、どうした
I-It makes my blood boil to ask you this...
あなたにこんなこといってたのはご。。。ほら
And more importantly it's a breach
of faith with the world, but...
するどころか
世界への配信なんだけど
Did you come here just to provoke me?!
挑発しに来たのか己は
Would you le... le...
きょうは　と。。と。。
"Le"?
と？
Le... let me stay the night here?
と、とめてもらえない。。。かしら
I... dropped my wallet...
財布を。。落としちゃって
Emilia the hero?!
勇者エミリオ
It's okay; she doesn't have
the energy to fight right now.
大丈夫
こいついま　戦う元気ネイから
How can you be so complacent, Sire?!
何を友情な
You are a ruler of demons! You cannot
party the night away with some hero!
魔王様ともあのお方か勇者と二人で御前様とは
We just got attacked.
Someone shot at us with magic bullets.
さっきそこで二人して襲われたんだよ
魔力弾で打たれた
Magic?!
魔力？！
So, she says she dropped her
wallet while we were running away.
で　逃げる途中で財布を落とししまったんだと
Apparently she lives over by Eifukucho.
That's a long walk, you know?
こいつ千江福町だったんけど
歩いて帰るには遠いしな
Are you saying she's staying
here for the night, Sire?!
つまり　ここに一晩をおいとくということですか
Don't just stand there, come in.
ほら　つっ立ってないではいれよ
Th-Thank you for having me.
お邪魔します
Just sit wherever. FYI, don't expect
any luxuries like a guest futon.
適当なところにすわってろ
言っとくが客用の布団が贅沢のもんはきたいすんなよ
I know, jeez.
分かってるわよ
What kind of attitude is that?!
King Satan is treating you with benevolence!
魔王様のお慈悲を下さっているのに
なんだその態度は
Pipe down, Ashiya, or the landlady will show up.
アシアうるせい
大家が来るぞ
Emi, take this.
エミ　これでもかぶったろ
That's the same detergent I use...
家のと同じ洗剤
If you want a pillow, use some magazines.
枕がほしけりゃ　その辺の雑誌を使え
I'll lend you 1,000 yen for now,
so get out of here on the first bus.
きょうのところは1000円貸してやるから
始発の時間にうせろよ
Okay.
The king graciously lent you those
thousand yen out of his meager savings!
魔王様は残り少ない財産からご貸し下さった千円だ
Treat it with respect!
大切に扱う
Yeah, yeah! I'll leave in the
morning, okay?! Thanks for the loan!
分かってますよ
朝になったらでていくわよ！
とおもう
Wench...
この女！
- We should turn in, too.
- Yes, Sire.
俺たちも寝るぞ
は！
I haven't let my guard down!
Don't try any funny business!
私は気を許したわけではないぞ
可笑しなまねはするなよ
Why am I doing this?
なんで私　こんなことしてるんだろう
We were pretty miserable at first, too, you know?
最初は俺なのずいぶん惨めな思いしただろう
Yes, Sire.
はあ。。。
And we were okay because there were two
of us, but it sounds like she's alone...
俺らは二人だったからよかったけど
あいつは一人みたいだし
You've grown soft, King Satan.
魔王様も甘くなられた
"From: (unknown address)"
"To: Sadao Maou"    "Sub: No subject"
"There are more earthquakes coming. Be careful."
「不明地址」
「地震将持续发生 请注意」
Who's this from?
誰だ？
Earthquakes?
地震？
What is this?
なんだこりゃ
Oh, I've got one from Chi too.
あっ　千チャンからも着てる
"There's going to be another earthquake.
What do I do?"
"There's going to be another
earthquake. What do I do?" Huh?
地震がまた起こります
どうしようって
Sire?
魔王様？
What's going on?
どういうことだ
この瞬間
在这瞬间
この場所がスダート
这里就是起点
イメージして見よう
试着想象一下
Where will morning start from, in this quiet sky?
何ができるのかな
我能做些什么
信じられない出来事だってある
会发生些不可思议的事吧
Fingertips twining in a pinky
swear I pretended not to see
もっと超えて行けるね
克服一切走的更远
If the moon's been laughed at,
she'll sink away toward yesterday
ゼロから生まれるすべて輝いて
从零重生的一切都特别耀眼
FLYあの空へ
翱翔朝着那片天空
Liar, coward... if I'm all these things at once
思い切り羽ばたきたい
想尽情地展翅
Then I only blossomed in dreams
最高のスマイルで笑いながら
以最完美的笑容
I hid in the moon's shadow,
but the truth is, I was crying
さぁ、行く
笑着前行吧
未知の世界へと　今飛び出そうよ
奔向未知的世界仿佛就要飞出来
The tears won't flow anymore...
did they all dry up?
未来を選び決めるのは自分
自己决定自己的未来
If I could forgive everything,
maybe they'd flow again
夢を追いかけて行　こう泣く日をある
追逐着梦想前进　也会有哭泣的日子
But these are all things I want to protect
それは大事な願い消えないで
珍贵的愿望不会消失
きっと会えるから
一定可以再次遇
明日の君
朝着未来的你
The Devil Goes on a Date with His Junior in Shinjuku